Advertisement

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: December 12, 2023

### GENERAL INFORMATION

At Spacebar Clicker, we are dedicated to safeguarding the privacy of all individuals who use our websites and applications, which are accessible globally. This Privacy Policy applies to all services and products offered by the Spacebar Clicker Website. Please note that we cannot be held responsible for the privacy policy of other sites and sources. Spacebar Clicker Website will act as the data controller in the framework of this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy and confirm that you are of legal age to consent to its terms. If there are any significant changes to this Privacy Policy, your continued use of the Site will indicate your acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy. At Spacebar Clicker Website, we value the privacy of all our users and are committed to ensuring that any personal information you provide is treated confidentially.

The Spacebar Clicker Website is intended for Website Visitors aged 16 and above. If you are under 16 years of age, you should not use this website. By accessing the Spacebar Clicker Site, you agree to comply with and be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. You also consent to the collection, processing, use, and disclosure of your data and information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using the Spacebar Clicker Site. If you are a parent or legal guardian and permit your child(ren) to access the Spacebar Clicker Site, you are also consenting to this Privacy Policy on their behalf.

We understand that you place your trust in us, and we take this responsibility seriously. On this page, we will explain what information we collect when you use our Site, why we collect it, and how we use it to enhance your user experience. This will give you a clear understanding of our practices. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at **[\[email protected\]](https://spacebarclicker.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**.

### WHICH DATA DO WE COLLECT?

#### Data you provide

We will only process personal data that you provide on a voluntary basis when you fill out the comment form on our Site or send us an email. This may include the following types of personal data:

* Name
* Email address
* Other information you choose to provide

#### Data we collect automatically

We may collect certain personal data through the use of cookies. For more information on this, please refer to Section Cookies of this Privacy Policy. We may also collect certain personal data without using cookies. This data can only be accessed and used during your visit to our Site and may include:

* Your IP address (used, e.g., for preventing double voting and location-based advertising)
* Your browser type and version
* The last Internet page you visited
* (Mobile) device IDs
* Cookie data
* User-level data (such as whether you viewed or clicked on an advertisement)

#### Data we receive from third parties

If we receive Personal Information from third parties, we will notify you personally.

### WHY DO WE COLLECT THESE DATA? BASED ON WHICH LEGAL GROUND?

In order to optimize our services and content, we will use your personal data, provided either by you directly or automatically collected through cookies and web beacons. Additionally, we may process your personal data if required by law, such as age verification. We may also use your personal data for direct marketing purposes, including updates on new and existing games and newsletters. Furthermore, we may also use your personal data for statistical purposes and to enhance our services and products. These activities are based on legitimate interests of the Spacebar Clicker Website.

Please note that advertisers on our website may collect information through cookies and/or web beacons for online behavioral advertising and/or multisite advertising. For more information about the use of cookies and web beacons, please refer to Section V below.

It's important to note that Spacebar Clicker is not responsible for any personal data collected by third-party software or methods on the Site, which may be subject to the third parties' general terms and conditions. We recommend that you avoid using your real name or email address when playing any of the games on our Site, particularly during multi-play.

Lastly, we have the right to share your data with all Google CPS Vendors so that Google DV360 may return GDPR compliant bids for ad delivery.

### DATA RETENTION PERIODS

We will only process your personal data for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Policy. Your personal data will be deleted one month after a period of consecutive years during which you have not visited our Site, unless we have a legitimate reason to retain your data, such as for customer relationship management.

### LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

We may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights
* To comply with the law

### YOUR DATA PROTECTION RIGHTS UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed about what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
* **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
* **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
* **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where we relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

### YOUR RIGHTS

If you no longer want to receive newsletters or information about our products or services, you can object to the processing of your personal data for these purposes at any time and without giving any justification. To do so, you can send us an email or contact us at the address provided below.

If you want to request the rectification or erasure of your personal data or restrict its processing, you should provide a specific reason for your request. Once we have verified and fulfilled these conditions, Spacebar Clicker Website will carry out your request as soon as possible and notify you accordingly.

### COOKIES

#### What are cookies?

Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer or device when you browse websites. They contain information related to the web browser and the specific website, and are saved in a designated folder on your hard drive. When you revisit a website, the cookie can be used to recognize the visitor and provide a personalized browsing experience based on their history. Web beacons are typically small, transparent graphic images that are placed on websites and used to monitor user behavior.

Cookies are used to improve the user experience by enhancing visitor friendliness. By using cookies to identify visitors, users do not have to repeatedly enter the same information, such as login credentials or screen settings, each time they visit a website.

#### Which kind of cookies exist?

Often, a distinction is made between two large groups of cookies:

**First-party cookies**: These cookies are created by the website you are visiting to enhance its performance. These cookies regulate the technical aspects of a site, such as language preferences or remembering items in an online shopping cart. First-party cookies are generated and placed by the visited website.

**Third-party cookies**: These cookies are created and placed on your device by a third-party other than the website you are visiting. They track a user's browsing behavior and are commonly used by social media platforms like Facebook and Twitter, as well as by tools like Google Analytics to measure website traffic.

Cookies that are necessary for the proper functioning of the site do not require permission. However, all other types of cookies do require permission.

#### Which cookies do we use?

We will only use first-party cookies to enhance your user experience while browsing the Site. These cookies record specific information about your visit, such as your language preference, the pages visited, and the duration of your visit.

In some cases, we may provide games from third-party game distributors on our portal. By playing a game provided by a third party, your Personal Data may be processed by them through the use of cookies or similar technology. It's important to note that playing a third-party game means you're playing within the environment of that game's developer, over which we have no control. We strongly recommend that you review the privacy policy of any game distributor before playing a game.

* Game Distribution: [Privacy Policy](https://static.gamedistribution.com/policy/privacy-platform.html)
* Game Monetize: [Privacy Policy](https://gamemonetize.com/privacypolicy)

By using the Site, you acknowledge and accept the possibility of third parties dropping cookies and/or using web beacons for advertising and tracking purposes. Third parties may use information gathered by cookies and/or web beacons for online behavioral advertising and/or multisite advertising, and the types of information gathered and purpose(s) of use are outlined in the privacy policies of said third parties. The Spacebar Clicker Website holds no liability for any third-party cookies or web beacons used for any purpose.

The Site may use third-party cookies, such as cookies from: \[list of third-party cookies\]

* Appnexus - [Privacy Policy](https://about.ads.microsoft.com/en-us/solutions/xandr/xandr-premium-programmatic-advertising)
* Google Ad Exchange - [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)
* Google Adsense - [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)
* Magnite - [Privacy Policy](https://www.magnite.com/legal/advertising-technology-privacy-policy/)
* Index Exchange - [Privacy Policy](http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/)
* Pubmatic - [Privacy Policy](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* Amazon - [Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)
* OpenX - [Privacy Policy](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* Sonobi - [Privacy Policy](https://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/)
* AppMonet - [Privacy Policy](https://appmonet.com/privacy-policy/8)
* TripleLift - [Privacy Policy](https://triplelift.com/privacy/)
* IpOnWeb - [Privacy Policy](https://www.iponweb.com/privacy-policy/)
* Media.net - [Privacy Policy](https://www.media.net/privacy-policy/)
* Sharethrough - [Privacy Policy](https://www.sharethrough.com/privacy-center/website-privacy-notice)
* YieldMo - [Privacy Policy](https://yieldmo.com/privacy-policy/)
* Smaato - [Privacy Policy](https://www.smaato.com/privacy/)
* Fluct - [Privacy Policy](https://corp.fluct.jp/privacy/ads/)
* SmartAdServer - [Privacy Policy](https://smartadserver.com/end-user-privacy-policy/)
* Unruly - [Privacy Policy](https://unruly.co/legal/privacy/)
* Venatus - [Privacy Policy](https://venatus.com/privacy)
* Headerlift - [Privacy Policy](https://www.headerlift.com/privacy.html)
* OneTag - [Privacy Policy](https://www.onetag.com/privacy/)
* Adagio - [Privacy Policy](https://adagio.io/privacy)

In addition, our website utilizes third-party cookies, including cookies provided by Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a free service offered by Google that enables website administrators to gather and analyze detailed statistics of website traffic, visitor flows, and page views. This valuable data provides insights to help improve the user experience by tailoring website content and features to the interests and behaviors of visitors.

#### How to manage cookies?

To manage cookies, you can adjust your browser settings to block cookies or only accept cookies from certain websites. Here is an overview of how to manage cookies in different browsers:

**Google Chrome**: Click the Chrome menu, then choose Settings. Click display advanced settings and then the button Settings for content in the 'Privacy' section. In the 'Cookies' section, you can edit your cookie settings and remove cookies.

**Internet Explorer**: Open your browser, click Tools, then Internet Options. Click the 'Privacy' section and choose the level you want with the slide control. You can also change this manually by clicking Advanced. A distinction is made between permanent direct cookies (first-party cookies), permanent indirect cookies (third-party cookies), and temporary cookies (session cookies). You can remove cookies by means of the main screen of internet options.

**Mozilla Firefox**: Open your browser and select Privacy. Set Firefox to use adapted settings for history. To switch cookies on, put a checkmark next to Accept cookies from websites. To turn off cookies, remove this checkmark. Firefox also gives you the possibility to switch off cookies from third parties (third-party cookies). Furthermore, you can set how long cookies can be kept. Click Show Cookies, and you can remove one or several cookies.

**Safari**: Open your browser. In Safari, cookie management is limited to one screen. Click on Preferences, and then select Privacy. You can choose to accept cookies, block cookies, or only accept cookies from certain websites. To remove cookies, click on Show Cookies.

**Opera**: Open the Opera browser, click the Extra menu, and then Preferences. Via Advanced and Cookies, you can set your cookie settings. You also have the possibility of having new cookies removed automatically when you close each Internet session. Moreover, you can decide about each cookie that is sent to your computer. You do this by clicking Ask me before accepting cookies. Each time a site wants to save a cookie, a dialog box is displayed.

### SECURITY MEASURES

Spacebar Clicker Website has implemented reasonable and appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure the secure processing of your Personal Information. If you have any inquiries about these security measures, please do not hesitate to contact us using the address provided below.

Personal data within the Spacebar Clicker Website is only accessible to individuals who require access in connection with their job.

At no point in time will we directly sell or rent out your personal data to third parties. However, we may occasionally use an external processor, in which case we will ensure that your information is handled confidentially and securely. The processor is not permitted to use your data on its own initiative, and your data must be erased as soon as the processor has completed the assigned task.

### CONTACT INFORMATION OF DATA CONTROLLER

If you have any inquiries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please reach out to us at **[\[email protected\]](https://spacebarclicker.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)** or through our contact form.
